Now that we've finished build the UI for our app,
it's time to think about how it should operate when it's
not in the foreground. One of the most powerful features of
Android, is the ability for any app to run in the
background. But with great power comes great responsibility. So, you need
to be very conscious of how it's consuming resources. In this
lesson, you'll learn more about how the Android framework manages background
apps and you'll be introduced to the service class to help
make that happen. You'll also learn techniques for efficient
data transfers using sync adapters and Google Cloud messaging. And
be introduced to the notification framework to send messages
to your users when your app isn't in the foreground.